League of Women Voters of Saratoga County; Records apap339
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Project and Subject Files, 1968-2010; 3; 1.4 cubic ft.
  - Groundwater Protection Grant - Application and Press Release, 1981-1982; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Groundwater Protection Grant - Grant Award and Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Groundwater Protection Grant - Public Education Newsclippings, 1982 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Information & Referral Study and Grant - Background and Consensus, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Information & Referral Study and Grant - Provider Proposal and Timetable, 1989; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Information & Referral Study and Grant - Report to Founder (Gannett), 1989 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Information & Referral Study and Grant - Results, 1990 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Information & Referral Study and Grant - RFP, 1989; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Information & Referral Study and Grant - Survey, 1979 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Information & Referral Study and Grant - Survey and Meetings, 1989; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Letters (Advocacy), 1967-1969; 1973-1974; 1976; 1981-1988 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Library Funding Study, 1990; 1995-1997; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Media Center Committee - Background, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Media Center Committee - Cable TV and Public Access, 1999; 2002; 2005; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Media Center Committee - Public Outreach, 2004-2005; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Meet the Candidates, 2001 October 29 (Video-tape 4)
  - Meet the Candidates, 2003 May 28 (Video-tape 5)
  - Meet the Candidates - Clifton Park, 2002 October 31 (Video-tape 6)
  - Meet the Candidates - Clifton Park, 2004 October 18 (Video-tape 7)
  - Meet the Candidates - Clifton Park/Halfmoon, Undated (Video-tape 8)
  - Meet the Candidates - Saratoga County Supervisors, Undated (Video-tape 9)
  - Meet the Candidates - Saratoga Springs Area, 2004 October 19 (Video-tape 10)
  - Meet the Candidates - Saratoga Springs Area - Complete Version, 2004 October 19 (Video-tape 11)
  - Meet the Candidates - Saratoga Springs Area, Undated (Video-tape 12)
  - Milk Cartons to Encourage Voting, Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Nonpartisan Political Policy, 1991; 1994-1998 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Nuclear Arms Forum, 1982; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Polling Place Accessibility, 1984 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Polling Place Accessibility - ADA Act and Checklist, 2001; 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Ballston, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Blank Form and Press Release, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Charleston and Galway, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Clifton Park and Halfmoon, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Greenfield, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Instrument and Training, 2006; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Malta, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Milton, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Northumberland, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Retroactive Contract, 2007 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Saratoga Springs, 2003-2004; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Saratoga Springs and Wilton, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Stillwater, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Surveys and Results, 2006 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Polling Place Accessibility Survey - Training Materials, 2006; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Racial Profiling Consensus Report, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Roohan, Margaret - Obituary, 1992 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Russian Delegation - AED Program, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Russian Delegation - Arrangements for Community Visits, 2004; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Russian Delegation - Budget and Acceptance, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Russian Delegation - Budget, Arrangement, Expense Report, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - Russian Delegation - Communications, 2002; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - Russian Delegation - Communications, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - Russian Delegation - Community Profile, 2002; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - Russian Delegation - Cultural Orientation Handbook, 1999 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - Russian Delegation - Final Report and Schedules, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 84)
  - Russian Delegation - Final Report and Schedules, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - Russian Delegation - Forms, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 86)
  - Russian Delegation - Gifts, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 87)
  - Russian Delegation - Host Packet, 2002; Undated (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 88)
  - Russian Delegation - News Clippings, 2002 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 89)
  - Russian Delegation - News Clippings, 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 90)
  - Russian Delegation -New York Times Booklet, ca. 2004 (Box 1 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 91)
  - Russian Delegation - Nuclear Controversy, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Russian Delegation - Open World Information, 1999-2000; Undated (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Russian Delegation - Participant Profiles, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Russian Delegation - Participant Profiles, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Russian Delegation - Photographs, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Russian Delegation - Photographs, 2004 (Cd 2)
  - Russian Delegation - Photographs, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Russian Delegation - Photo Negatives, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Russian Delegation - Photo Negatives, 2004 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Russian Delegation - Services Arranged, 2002 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Russian Delegation - Sheelagh Bailys Photographs, 2004 October 30 (Cd 3)
  - Russian Delegation - Translators, 2002; Undated (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Russian Delegation - Translators, ca. 2004 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Russian Delegation Visit, 2004 (Video-tape 13)
  - Saratoga County Health Department Consensus, 1988 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Activity, 1965; 1967-1969 (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Activity, 1974-1976; 1979; Undated (Box 2 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Activity, 1983-1985; 1991; Undated (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Local Law Amendments, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Review, 1975 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter Text, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Saratoga Springs City Charter, 2006 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Student Voters Articles, 1988 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Student Voting Rights - Court Cast Establishing, 1985 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Student Voting Rights - LWV Information, 1998; 2003; Undated (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Student Voting Rights - Skidmore Court Case, 1988 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Student Voting Rights - Skidmore Polling Site Problems, 2003-2004 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Sunshine Week - Grant Application and Final Report, 2005-2006; Undated (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Sunshine Week - News Clippings, 2006 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Sunshine Week - Openness in Government Forums, 2007 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Sunshine Week - Sample Packet, 2006 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Voting Machine Lobby Packet, 2005 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Voter's Services, Candidate Responses, 1973-1975; 1977; 1986 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Water Study, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Project and Subject Files), Folder 17)